address007.com 2017-11-29

# Address007.com Privacy policy Page

In continuity of availing numerous services we provide from time to time through our website www.address007.com (you may be required to give your Name, Address, Email id, D.O.B and similar Personal Information). The PI (Personal Information) is used for the purposes: to revise the information you see, to meet your requests for certain services, and to contact you about our services.

Except otherwise stated explicitly, this Policy applies to Personal Info. as disclosed on any of the Media.

We give our commitment to give protection to the privacy and confidentiality of all Personal Info. That you may share with us as a user. In advancement thereof, we have this policy to make evident our good faith.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or to people that we do not employ or manage.

Your Personal Information will be kept secret and will be used for our research, marketing, and strategic client analysis objectives and other internal business purposes only.

We do not share, sell or rent Personal Information for advertising purposes without your advance permission to the third parties.

In advancement of the secrecy with which we treat PI we have put in place desired physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We make you able to edit your account information and preferences at any time. To safeguard your privacy and security, we will also take responsibility to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

You ratify that you are disclosing Personal Info. with your own will.

we are no way responsible for the information presented on websites like [address0007.net](https://address0007.net/), [allservicecenters.net](https://allservicecenters.net/), [allcustomercarenumbers.net](https://allcustomercarenumbers.net/), [customercarenumbers.net](https://customercarenumbers.net/), [allbusinessnumbers.com](https://allbusinessnumbers.com/), [findbusinessaddress.com](https://findbusinessaddress.com/), [addressofcustomerservicenumber.com](https://addressofcustomerservicenumber.com/), [customerservicecontactphonenumber.com](https://customerservicecontactphonenumber.com/) and many more sites like this. so we request you to contact the website owner of these websites for any issue rather than contacting [ address007.com](https://address007.com/)  
If you are our corporate client, it is acceptable that we have entered into a contract with you for non-disclosure of confidential information. The contract should not be affected by this Policy in any manner.

If you have queries or concerns about this policy; please contact us via contact us page below.

**Third Party ad Networks**  
By using address007.com you agree and accept that third party ad networks that are serving ads on address007.com may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving.
